lasikplus.com 2018-08-20

# LasikPlus Website Privacy Policy

LCA-Vision Inc. d/b/a Lasik _Plus (_ “We” or “Us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information.    

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how We collect, use and share the information We receive from you or that you may provide to Us including when you visit our website _[www.lasikplus.com](https://www.lasikplus.com/) _(“Website”).  This Policy also describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing your information.

_**This Policy Applies to Information We Collect or Receive:**_

  * Via the Internet and mobile space including via our Website
  * When you schedule an appointment with Us
  * When you request further information from Us about laser vision correction
  * When you submit information to the Website such as testimonials regarding your experience with laser vision correction

Please read this Policy carefully to understand our procedures regarding your information.  By accessing this Website, you agree to this Policy.  We may change this Policy from time to time (see “Changes to Privacy Policy” below).  Your continued use of this Website after We make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes.

_**Children Under the Age of 18**_

Our Website is not intended for children under 18 years of age.  We do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under 18.  If you are under 18, do not provide any information to this Website including your name, address, telephone number, or email address.  If We learn that We have collected or received Personally Identifiable Information from a child under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.  If you believe we may have information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at _[privacy@lasikplus.com](mailto:privacy@lasikplus.com)_. 

_**Information We Collect About You**_

We collect several types of information including:

  * Information by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted (“Personally Identifiable Information”); and
  * Information that does not individually identify you, such as your gender, age, or other demographic information.

_**Information You Provide to Us**_

The information you may provide to Us may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling out forms on our Website. This includes information provided in order to schedule an appointment with us, or in order to receive further information regarding laser vision correction.    
  * Information to be posted on public areas of the Website (“User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on the Website at your own risk.  Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

_**Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies**_

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, We may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, geolocation data, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include Personally Identifiable Information. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * _Cookies_. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * _Flash Cookies_. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects, or flash cookies, to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. 
  * _IP Address_. Your IP Address is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider. An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses our applications or websites, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels, helping diagnose server problems, and administering the websites. We may also derive your approximate location from your IP Address.

_**How We Use Your Information**_

We use information that We collect about you or that you provide to Us, including any Personally Identifiable Information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you
  * To provide you with information (e.g. InfoKits) regarding laser vision correction that you request from us
  * To notify you about changes to our Website 
  * To allow you to participate in any interactive features on our Website
  * To facilitate e-mail or phone contact with you
  * In any other way We may describe when you provide the information

We use your IP Address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our Website and to gather demographic information. Our third party ad servers will also provide us with summary, but not individual, reports that will tell us what you clicked on. We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide our services to you.  We will also use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our Website, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze our Website’s use, and customize the Website’s content and layout.  We require your opt-in consent for the sharing of any Personally Identifiable Information with third parties. We will not sell, distribute or lease your Personally Identifiable Information or use your Personally Identifiable Information to send you promotional information about third parties, unless you have given us your opt-in consent to do so.

_**Interest-Based Advertising**_

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements to you when you access our Website based on information relating to your access to and use of other websites, applications or online services on any of your devices. To do so, these companies may use various technologies, including the placement or recognition of a unique cookie on your browser (including through use of pixel tags). They may also use these technologies, along with information they collect about your online use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile phone and a laptop. These companies use the information they collect, as well as information received from third parties, to serve ads for us and others about goods and services that may be of interest to you when you are on our Website or on third-party properties.

_**Disclosure of Your Information**_

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information that We collect or you provide:

  * To our employees, subsidiaries and affiliates
  * To contractors or service providers we use to support our business
  * To comply with any law, court order or legal process, including to respond to any subpoena, governmental or regulatory investigation
  * For any purpose disclosed by Us when you provide the information
  * For any other purpose with your opt-in consent

_**Correcting Your Information**_

You may email Us at _[privacy@lasikplus.com](mailto:privacy@lasikplus.com)_ to request that We change or delete any information that you have provided to Us.  We may not accommodate a request to change or delete information if we believe the change or deletion would violate any law or regulation. 

_**Data Security**_

We have implemented measures designed to secure your information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure.  However, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your information, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of your information.

_**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**_

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time.  The date this Policy was last revised is identified below.  You are responsible for periodically checking this Policy for any updates.  Your continued use of this Website after We make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes. 

_**How to Opt Out**_

If you prefer not to receive mail, phone, text or email communications from us, you can opt out by clicking on the following link: _<https://www.lasikplus.com/unsubscribe> _

In addition, you can opt out of receiving email communications from us by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link that can be found at the bottom of every email we deliver, or by emailing us at _[privacy@lasikplus.com](mailto:privacy@lasikplus.com)_.

_**Contact Information**_

If you have any questions regarding this Policy or our privacy procedures, you may contact us as follows:

Email: _[privacy@lasikplus.com](mailto:privacy@lasikplus.com)_

Phone: 513-354-5836  

Last revised February 15, 2018
